♪ Get up, get up, get up, get up ♪
♪ Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up ♪
♪ Oooh baby, now let's get down tonight ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
♪ Baby, I'm hot just like an oven ♪
♪ I need some loving ♪
♪ And baby, I can't hold it much longer ♪
♪ It's getting stronger and stronger ♪
♪ And when I get that feeling ♪
♪ I want sexual healing ♪
♪ Sexual healing ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ Makes me feel so fine ♪
♪ Helps to relieve my mind ♪
♪ Sexual healing, baby, is good for me ♪
♪ Sexual healing is something
that's good for me ♪
♪ Whenever blue teardrops are falling ♪
♪ And my emotional
stability is leaving me ♪
♪ There is something I can do ♪
♪ I can get on the telephone
and call you up, baby ♪
♪ And honey, I know you'll
be there to relieve me ♪
♪ The love you give to me will free me ♪
♪ If you don't know the
thing you're dealing, oh ♪
♪ I can tell you, darling,
that it's sexual healing ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up, get up ♪
♪ Let's make love tonight ♪
♪ Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up ♪
♪ 'Cause you do it right ♪
♪ Baby, I got sick this morning ♪
♪ A sea was storming inside of me ♪
♪ And baby, I think I'm capsizing ♪
♪ The waves are rising and rising ♪
♪ And when I get that feeling ♪
♪ I want sexual healing ♪
♪ Sexual healing is good for me ♪
♪ Makes me feel so
fine, it's such a rush ♪
♪ Helps to relieve the
mind and it's good for us ♪
♪ Sexual healing, baby, is good for me ♪
♪ Sexual healing is something
that's good for me ♪
♪ And it's good for me and
it's so good for you, my baby ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oooh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Just take control ♪
♪ Just grab a hold of my body and mind ♪
♪ Soon we'll be making it, honey ♪
♪ Oh, you're doing fine ♪
♪ You're my medicine,
open up and let me in ♪
♪ Darling, you're so great ♪
♪ I can't wait for you to operate ♪
♪ Get up, get up, get up, get up ♪
♪ Let's make love tonight ♪
♪ Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up ♪
♪ 'Cause you do it right ♪
♪ Heal me, my darling ♪
♪ Heal me ♪
♪ I can't wait for you to operate ♪
♪ When I get this feeling,
I need sexual healing ♪
♪ Oh, when I get this feeling,
♪ I gotta have sexual healing, darling, ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm all alone ♪
♪ Sexual healing, darling,
till you come back home ♪
♪ Please don't procrastinate ♪
♪ It's not good to masturbate ♪